一个在Android里被使用最多的implicit intents是
One of the most used implicit intents
是这个分享Intent
in Android is the share intent. It's [LAUGH]
它非常棒  这是一个你和你朋友
awesome. It's a great way to waste time
用来消磨时间的一个很好的方式
for both you and your friends. [SOUND] [LAUGH].
丹
>> Dan!
你能使用你最喜欢的应用去分享相片  文字
>> You can leverage your favorite apps to share photos, texts,
视频和普通链接  而这最棒的部分就是你甚至无需
videos and general links. And the best part is you don't have
知道使用者最喜欢的应用是什么  仅需要告知
to even know what the user's favorite apps are. Just tell
系统你想要分享的是什么数据 然后给你的用户显示
Android what data you want to share and it shows your users
一系列能分享它的应用  有一些APP可能还
a list of apps that will share it. Apps that
并不存在，当你的APP正在被开发时  为了
may not have existed when you app was written. To
使分享更加容易，Android 4.0添加了
make it even easier to share Android 4.0 added the
ShareActionProvider  同时我们也把它加入到了早先的Android版本
share action provider and we have it for previous releases of
以支持库的形式  它通过使用Intent
Android as part of a support library. It operates using
的ACTION_SEND来实现这个操作
the action send intent.
它会把请求发送给每一个能执行的ACTION_SEND的Activity
it would be addressed to anyone who could perform action
要发送的数据会以extras的形式被包含在Intent里
send. The data it sent would be included with it as extras
要么作为文本或者二进制数据的URI
either as text, or URI to the binary data. And
MIME(多用途网络邮件扩展）类型会标明这个URI指向的内容
the MIME type would indicate what the URI points to.
这就是ShareActionProvider所带给
Here's what the share action provider will bring to
我们的应用。 让人喜欢的线框图
our app: the glorious wire frame. There will be
这里多出一个图标在操作栏里 当点击这个图标时
an additional icon in the action bar which will
有一个下拉菜单会弹出来展示所有可能
drop down a menu when clicked to reveal potential
的分享操作。另一个图标会被添加在
share actions. Another icon will be added to the
这个图标的右边，它是上一次分享所使用的APP
right of this one that contains the last application
添加一个ShareActionProvider到DetailActivity的
shared to. Add a ShareActionProvider to the fragment within
Fragment里面。它能按照这个格式分享天气
DetailActivity. It will share weather in the following format.
是的  就仅仅是我们传递进这个View的字符串加上#SunshineApp
Yes, it's just the string we passed into the view plus #SunshineApp.